familyoven.com 2007-06-25

# Family Oven - - Reverse Recipe Search Results - FamilyOven.com

Janurary 15, 2007 

At FamilyOven we recognize that privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use FamilyOven's services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. 

## Scope

This notice offers highlights of the full FamilyOven Privacy Policy, which describes in detail the privacy practices that apply to FamilyOven's products, services and websites worldwide (collectively, FamilyOven's "services"). You can also get more information about the privacy practices for specific FamilyOven services in the navigation bar to the left of this notice. Personal information and other data we collect 

  * FamilyOven collects personal information when you register for a FamilyOven service or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. 
  * FamilyOven uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and save information like search history and saved links. 
  * FamilyOven's servers automatically record information when you visit our website or use some of our products, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request. 

## Uses 

  * We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. 
  * We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve FamilyOven technologies and services. 
  * We may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties outside of FamilyOven. 
  * When we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
  * We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services. 
  * FamilyOven processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries 

## Your choices 

  * We offer you choices when we ask for personal information, whenever reasonably possible. You can find more information about your choices in the privacy notices or FAQs for specific services. 
  * You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result. 
  * We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible. 

## More information 

For information about specific FamilyOven services, please check the relevant privacy notice in the navigation bar to the left. FamilyOven is a member of the EU/US Safe Harbor Program. If you have additional questions, please contact us any time.
